电视:今晚还将播出史蒂文的警察摇滚.
TV: And coming up late tonight Steven Botchcoes cop Rock.
麦琪:好了,克莉丝,我们两个头得走了.
Maggie: Ok Chrissy, its time for us top leave.
克莉丝:妈妈.你们很晚才能回家吗,
Chrissy: Mum.Are you going to be home late,
否则我要错过警察摇滚了.
or am I going to have to miss Cop rock?
麦琪:亲爱的,那过了你的上床时间.
Maggie: Honey it's passed your bedtime.
克莉丝:但是电视很精彩.
Chrissy: But its breakthrough television.
麦琪:睡觉去.晚安.克莉丝.
Maggie: Go to bed.Goodnight.Chrissy.You won't be needing that.
你不需要看那.开萝尔,我指望你保证……
Carol, I'm counting on you to make sure...
开萝尔:克莉丝八点半进被窝.是,是,是.
Carol: Chrissy's in bed by eight thirty.Yeah, yeah, yeah.
杰森:这就是你为什么抱怨照看他们了?
Jason: So why are you complaining about babysitting?
今天晚上又不是你约会的日子.
It's not like you had a date tonight.
开萝尔:你们走吧.
Carol: Just go.
本:好了,今天晚上我已经把盘子洗干净了,
Ben: Well, I'm all done on doing the dishes on a night that's not even
尽管还没有轮到我.
my turn.
杰森:很好,本.
Jason: That's good Ben.
本:豌豆色拉真好,妈妈.有味,而且无害.
Ben: That was great bean salad mum.Interesting but not dangerous.
麦琪:谢谢,本.
Maggie: Thanks Ben.
本:我能得到你的秘诀吗?
Ben: May I have your recipe.
杰森:对你没用.我们还要去晚上的家长会.
Jason: It won't do you any good.We're still going top parents night.
本:今晚?
Ben: Is that tonight?
杰森:哦,我是不是找个时间收拾他了?
Jason: Oh, should I ground him now or later.
本:我我现在可没有跟以前一样调皮,那样是什么时候的事情了?
Ben: This isn't like all those times I go in trouble, way back, when was that?
杰森:哦,上个学期.
Jason: Oh, lat semester.
本:嘿,瞧.
Ben: Hey look, what I'm saying is that I'm more mature When was the last
我说我成熟多了.你们上次看见我用鼻子吹牛奶是什么时候?
time you guys saw me blow milk through my nose?.
麦琪:好了.
Maggie: Well,
本:那可不算,那不是牛奶.
Ben: Hey it doesn't count though, it wasn't milk.
而且那天我得了优,也就是自己保密.
And just the other day I had gas and I kept it all to myself.
麦琪:本!
Maggie: Ben!
本:不全是我自己知道,但……
Ben: hey not completely to myself, but...
麦琪:好的,亲爱的,
Maggie: Ok, look honey, we have noticed that you are more mature.
我们已经注意到了你变成熟了.你已经几个星期没有惹事了,
You haven't gotten into any trouble for weeks, your grades are fine,
你的成绩不错,我猜你把所有老师给吸引了.
and my guess is you've got all your teachers buffaloed.
本:我猜是.
Ben: You bet I do.
杰森:我们动身了,麦琪.
Jason: Let's roll Maggie.
本:记住他们是挣不到什么钱的苦命人.
Ben: Remember these are bitter people who don't make a lot of money.
麦琪:谢谢你,你花时间了.考克梅尔老师.
Maggie: Well thank you for your time Mrs.Crockmyer.
杰森:是的,很高兴和你交谈.
Jason: Yes, I'm glad we got to talk.
听说本这么认真,真的很开心.
Its great to hear Ben's finally buckling down like that.
老师:我喜欢教孩子,也喜欢解剖青蛙.
Teacher: Well I like teaching children and I like cutting up frogs.
麦琪:那不是英语课吗?
Maggie: But isn't this an English class?
老师:是英语课.
Teacher: Yes.
麦琪:考克梅尔老师……
Maggie: Mrs.Crockmyer...
杰森:等会,我们今晚很愉快.
Jason: Wait, we're having a great night.
有十六个老师夸奖本.
That's the sixth teacher who's been glowing about Ben.
麦琪:自从迈克进来后,他们肯定降低了评价标准.
Maggie: They sure must have lowered their standards since mike went her.
校长:注意,父母们.
Principal: Attention parents.This is your beloved principle Willis Dewitt.
这是你们亲爱的校长Willis Dewitt.接下来是午餐.
Next period is lunch.
在这段时间,
During this period you are welcome to come to my office to get your child's
你们可以去我办公室取你们孩子的橱柜钥匙.这样你们可以检查他们的私人物品.
locker combination.So you can route through their personal belongings.
麦琪:哦.
Maggie: Oh!
杰森:麦琪,我们不必检查本的橱柜.
Jason: Maggie, we don't have to route through bens locker.
麦琪:当然,我们不必.我们得去.
Maggie: Of course we don't have to.We get to.
杰森:麦琪.本不会对我们隐藏什么的.
Jason: Maggie.Ben wouldn't hide anything from us.
麦琪:因为他是好学生?
Maggie: Because he's such a good student?
杰森:不,因为再狡猾,也骗不了我们.
Jason: No because he's not slick enough to get anything passed us.
麦琪:哦,杰森,你准备站在这里,什么都不干?
Maggie: Oh Jason, are you going to stand here and do nothing?
杰森:不.我准备去男洗手间方便.
Jason: No.I'm going to go to the boy's room and do something.
男人:嗨,当心.哈,被迫的习惯.
Man: Hey, look up.Um, hu, force of habit.
杰森:人,人,
Jason: Men, men, men, men, men.
人,人,
How can we be expected to have our children follow our example if we
人,人呀.如果我们自己不树立榜样,
ourselves don't set it?
我们怎么要求我们的孩子以我们为榜样?好了,
Come on, the surgeon generals report is a generation old.
医生的报告已经过时了.我们是不是该点火了?
Isn't it time that we need light?
男人:谢谢.点着了.
Man: No thanks.It's lit.
杰森:这里的男孩使我想起了过去.我记得在我学校,
Jason: Boy this takes me back.
在这获得真正的教育.
I remember in my school, this is where you get your real education.Mr.
小先生咬人.是不是有意思?
little bites.Isn't that funny.
男人2:没有意思.我是小先生.
Man 2: No.I'm Mr.little.
杰森:我说这很有讽刺意味,他们说些不体面的事情,
Jason: I meant that it's ironic that they should say something so
还用亲切的先生的习惯表达.
disrespectful and then
still use the traditional expression of "good will Mr
男人:你这个蠢货是谁?
Man: What kind of goof ball are you?
杰森:精神病医生.
Jason: Psychiatrist.
男人:啊哈.
Man: Uh hu.
杰森:西维尔医生.
Jason: Dr Seaver.
朗达的父亲:西维尔医生.
Ronda's Father: Dr Seaver!
杰森:你好.
Jason: Hello.
朗达的父亲:哦,嗨,西维尔医生.嗨!
Ronda's Father: Ho.Hey, doctor Seaver.Hey!
杰森:嗨!
Jason: Hey!
朗达的父亲:你好,莫.
Ronda's Father: Hey mo.
杰森:莫!
Jason: Mo!
朗达的父亲:莫 格林.
Ronda's Father: Mo Green.
杰森:莫 格林.
Jason: Mo Green.
朗达的父亲:朗达的爸爸.
Ronda's Father: Ronda's dad.
杰森:那就是朗达 格林.
Jason: That would be Ronda Green.
朗达的父亲:我知道她是本的朋友.哦,我喜欢那个小傻瓜.
Ronda's Father: I know she is friends with Ben.Oh I love that knucklehead.
杰森:是吗?
Jason: You do?
朗达的父亲:如果我不喜欢他,
Ronda's father: If I didn't,
我怎么可能让他一周来六个晚上?
how else could I put with him for six nights a week?
杰森:一周六个晚上.
Jason: Six nights week?
朗达的父亲:是呀,他已经是我们家里的一员了.
Ronda's Father: Yeah, he's practically part of the family.
杰森:本 西维尔?
Jason: Ben Seaver?
朗达的父亲:你打住,你这样子要笑死我.
Ronda's Father: Will you stop it, you're killing me.
我正想恭喜你.他是个好孩子,
I'm going to compliment you.He's a great kid, and such a hard worker.
而且是个干活卖力.打扫车库,洗碗,
Cleaning the garage, washing the dishes, fixing the plumbing.
装管道.是不是所有转变都是你教的?
Was it you that taught him all about transmissions?
杰森:西-维-尔?
Jason: S E A V E R?
朗达的父亲:我不知道,我也不知道怎么拼写.
Ronda's Father: I don't know.I can't spell.I'm illiterate.
我是文盲.我就是高兴我们能遇见,因为如果近期我们结为亲家的话,
I'm just so glad we're getting along because I wouldn't be surprised if
我一点也不奇怪.你知道我在说什么吗?
one of these days, you and me were related.If you know what I mean?
杰森:你到底在说些什么?
Jason: What the hell are you talking about?
朗达的父亲:本和朗达.
Ronda's Father: Ben and Ronda.
嘿,你现在装着你什么都不知道,
Hey, now how come you're acting like you don't know what's going on when
那么你给他们举办宏大的六周纪念晚会的时候干什么去了?
you threw them a big six-week anniversary party, hu?
杰森:麦琪!过来,
Jason: Maggie!Come on in here, there's something I want you to hear.
我得让你听听一些事情.朗达的父亲:哦,我喜欢你儿子.
Ronda's Father: Oh, I love this guy.
麦琪:如果他跟她约会了六个星期的哈,为什么我们没有碰见?
Maggie: Well if he's been dating her for six weeks, why haven't we met her?
杰森:我不知道.
Jason: I don't know.
麦琪:那么他是怎么连续六周从家里偷偷跑出去的?
Maggie: And how could he sneak out of the house very night for six weeks?
杰森:我也不知道.
Jason: I don't know.
麦琪:杰森,那么你知道什么?
Maggie: Jason, what do you know?
杰森:我知道我不喜欢被人抓住.
Jason: I know I don't like getting noogied.
麦琪:本呢?
Maggie: Where's Ben?
开萝尔:不说晚上好?不对我照看孩子说谢谢?不感谢我花了时间?
Carol: No good evening?No thank you for babysitting?No gratitude for my time?
麦琪:够了.本在哪儿?
Maggie: That's right.Where's Ben?
开萝尔:不知道,我也不关心.
Carol: Don't know, don't care.
麦琪:呵.就你这样的态度,
Maggie: Hu.With an attitude like that its no wonder that little Ben is
怪不得小本偷偷出去和那个十四岁的姑娘约会,他的橱柜里居然有连裤袜.
sneaking around with this fourteen-year-old girl with pantyhose in his locker.
开萝尔:什么?你认为我态度不好?好啊!
Carol: What?You think I have an attitude?Well hu!
本:怎么了,
Ben: Well, you guys must be really hungry after hearing all those great
你们在听了我的所有伟大事迹之后一定饿了吧.
things about me.
杰森:本,这是我一生中对你最失望的一次.
Jason: Ben, I've never been more disappointed in you in my whole life.
本:呵,嗨,把老师休息室里的厕所坐位抹上凡士林可不是我的主意.
Ben: Uh, hey, it wasn't my idea to Vaseline the toilet seats in the teachers lounge.
麦琪:啊哈.
Maggie: Uh hu.
本:他们准备把解剖后的青蛙扔掉,
Ben: Hey they were going to throw out those dissected frogs anyway,
我为什么不利用呢?
so why could I use them?
杰森:我给你一些提示,本.呢,呢,呢,呢,呢.
Jason: Let me give you a hint Ben.Ni ni ni ni ni.
本:你知道莫.
Ben: You know mo.
杰森:比你想像的要多.
Jason: Mo than you think.
本:我想我没有理由再说什么了,但是晚安.
Ben: Well I guess there's no reason for me to say anything but goodnight.
麦琪:别指望开溜,先生.
Maggie: Don't count on it Mr.
杰森:为什么我们没有碰见朗达?
Jason: Why haven't we met Ronda?
麦琪:六周!
Maggie: Six weeks!
杰森:家庭的一份子.
Jason: Part of the family.
麦琪:没有允许的前提下擅自改装转播设备.
Maggie: Fixing transmissions without permission.
杰森:别就作在那里.说话.
Jason: Don't just sit there.Say something.
本:我真的,真的,真的爱你们.
Ben: I really, really, really love you guys.
杰森:啊哈.
Jason: Uh hu.
本:好,听着.我跟叫朗达的女孩约会.
Ben: Ok look.I'm dating this girl named Ronda.There, it's out in the open.
这样,坦白了.我感觉好多了.
I feel better.
麦琪:从开始讲,本,
Maggie: From the beginning Ben, and include all the lies,
包括所有的谎言,虚假和诡计.
falsehood and deceptions.
本:嗯……
Ben: Um...
杰森:我在等你解释呢,本.
Jason: I'm waiting for the old ripple dissolve Ben.
本:是这样,在上学的第一周还是第二周,
Ben: Well, it was during the first or second week of school.
这点我不确定,但是我知道是在我的英语课之后,
I'm not sure, but I know it was after my English class,
因为我鞋子上弄上青蛙血了.
because there was frog blood on my shoes.
当我看见他的时候,我正从我的橱柜里拿我的午饭.
I was getting lunch from my locker when I saw her.
朗达:这是我最后一次穿白色的鞋子上英语课.
Ronda: That's the last time I wear white shoes to English class.
本:你在我的班上?
Ben: You're in my class?
朗达:是的.我没想过高中英语会是这样.
Ronda: Yeah.I had no idea high school English would be like this.
你想去看电影吗?
Do you want to go out to a movie?
本:嗯?
Ben: Hu?
朗达:哦,好.
Ronda: Oh right.I'm Ronda Green,
我叫朗达 格林,我想你可能很忙,会忘记我的邀请.
but you are probably busy so just forget I asked.
本:等等,等等,等会儿.你让我出去约会?
Ben: Wait, wait wait a minute.You're asking me out on a date?
朗达:你装的好象以前你没有遇到过这样的事情一样.
Ronda: You're acting like it's never happened to you before.
本:开玩笑?通常有成群结队的女孩子约我.
Ben: Are you kidding?Usually it's groups of women asking me out.
朗达:那么,哪个晚上?
Ronda: So, what night?
本:随便哪个晚上.
Ben: Any night.
朗达:我那时也有空.
Ronda: I'm free then too.
本:好的,放学后,我们仔细讨论.在垃圾后面.
Ben: Ok, we'll work the details out after school.Behind the dumpster.
朗达:那里臭气熏天?
Ronda: The one that smells really bad?
本:我也很清楚.
Ben: I know it well.
朗达:哦,你不必担心,
Ronda: Oh and just so you don't worry, I'll pay for me.
我自己付帐.我不是看在你的钱的份上.
I'm not after your money.
本:我喜欢你的风格.花花公子,花花公子.嗨,伙计.干什么呢?
Ben: I like your style.Dudes, dudes.Hey guys.What's happening?
斯丁克:我今天开始刮胡子.
Stinky: I started shaving today.
本:是的,斯丁克,
Ben: Yeah Stink, but your back doesn't count.
但是你后面还有数不清的.那么,你们打算这个周末干什么?
So uh, what do you guys figure we're doing this weekend?
朋友:我不知道.我会待在家里,
Friend: I don't know.
然后一切由我大哥摆布.
I was going to stay home and let my big brother push me around.
斯丁克:他会摆布我吗?
Stinky: Will he push me too?
本:对不起,我不能加入你们,但是我有个约会.
Ben: Sorry I can't join you guys but I got a date.
朋友:啊,马戏团会到镇里了.西维尔,你约谁呢?
Friend: Ah, the circus is back in town.So Seaver, who did you ask out?
本:我没有约任何人出来.她约的我.
Ben: I didn't ask anybody out.She asked me.
男孩:狗屁!
Guys: No way!
本:你们装成这样,好象以前没有碰见这事.
Ben: You guys act like this has never happened to you before.
斯丁克:我遇到过一个女孩,对我说"什么味道?"
Stinky: I had a girl talk to me once.She said, "What smells in here?"
朋友:是呀,斯丁克,我大哥也会摆布你的.
Friend: Yeah stinky, my brother will push you around.
朋友2:谁约你?
Friend 2: Who asked you out?
本:朗达 格林.
Ben: Ronda Green.
伙伴们:搞笑.
Guys: Laughing.
本:有什么好笑的?
Ben: What's so funny?
朋友1:我们还以为你说的是个好姑娘,像拉拉队长,或者更好的.
Friend 1: We thought you meant a real woman, like a cheerleader, or better.
斯丁克:什么比拉拉队长还要好?
Stinky: What's better than a cheerleader?
朋友1:体操运动员.
Friend 1: A gymnast.
伙伴们:是呀!
Guys: Yeah!
本:你们就知道嫉妒我,因为没人约你们出去.
Ben: You guys are just dumping on me because no one asked you out.
朋友2:本,本,
Friend 2: Bennie, Bennie, she's not on the A list.
她不是一流的.如果你不和一流的姑娘去约会,你就完蛋了.
You go out with a girl who's not on the A list and you're finished.
你的社交生活就结束了,你最后就只能和乐队的女孩在一起.
Your social life is over and you'll end up with a girl in band.
斯丁克:我在乐队.
Stinky: I'm in band.
朋友2:说够多了.
Friend 2: Nough said.
本:但是她自己买单.
Ben: But she's paying her own way.
朋友2:因为她不得不.
Friend 2: Well because she has to.
朋友1:本,本,
Friend 1: Bennie, Bennie, check the wall of truth.
去看看真理墙吧.
There is something disgusting and horrible about every girl on the A list,
那里有每个一流的女孩子的一些可恶和可怕的事情,但是不幸的是你找不到朗达 格林的风流韵事.
unfortunately you wont find anything pornographic about Ronda Green.
本:斯丁克 苏利文是格有魅力的男人!
Ben: Stinky Sullivan is a hunk!
斯利文:我自己写的.等姑娘看呢.
Stinky: I wrote that.Wait till the girls read it.
朋友1:省省吧,斯丁克.姑娘什么时候进这里?
Friend 1: Think stinky.When will the girls be in this room?
斯丁克:当他们用浴室的时候.
Stinky: When they use the bathroom.
朋友2:本,听着,
Friend 2: Bennie, look, you can go out with her if you want.
如果你愿意,你可以和她出去.但是你也许变成一个过道管理员.
But you might as well become a hall monitor.
本:过道管理员.我!我告诉她取消这次约会.
Ben: Hall monitor.Me!I had to tell her that this date was off.
本:但是当她为了不闻臭气捏着鼻子的可爱样子,你怎么去伤她的心?
Ben: But how do you break a girls heart when she looks so cute holding
我知道,我打电话给她.
her nose from the stench?I know, I'll phone her.
朗达,我不去垃圾那里见你,
Rhonda, before you get mad at me for not meeting you at the dumpster,
你别生我的气,我要告诉你一些事情.
I got to tell you something.
我这周五不能和你出去的原因是…因为,我是个同性恋.
The reason I cant go out with you this Friday is... because, I'm gay.
这样她的心里会好受些,我也不用当兵了.
Hey that will spare her feelings and keep me out of the army.
迈克:嗨,本.
Mike: Hey Bennie.
本:你好.
Ben: Hi.
迈克:你干什么呢?
Mike: What are you doing?
本:没什么.
Ben: Nothing.
迈克:是你的屁股在通电话?
Mike: Is your but making a phone call?
本:迈克,我是个死人.
Ben: Mike, I'm a dead man.
那个约我出去的女孩不是一流的.
There's this girl who asked she s and me out not on the A list.
如果我和她出去约会,
And if I go out with her I'm in terrible trouble.
我会有达麻烦.我绝望了.
I'm at the end of my rope.
杰森:本,我们想知道你为什么和这个女孩出去约会,
Jason: Ben we want to know why you want to go out with this girl and
但是你给我们讲一些你不愿和她出去约会的荒谬事情.
you are telling us ridiculous stories about not wanting to go out with her.
本:我刚要谈到这点.
Ben: I was just getting to that.
杰森:我们听着呢.
Jason: Well get to it.
本:好吧;那是因为迈克搅和进来.
Ben: Ok.Well that's when mike got involved.
迈克:哇.
Mike: Wow.
杰森:等会儿,迈克.回来.
Jason: Wait a minute Mike.Get back here.
迈克:不,我不会对这小子负责.
Mike: No, I'm not responsible for this little guy.
我是说,我可不象他.无论他做什么,
I mean I don't even like him.
是他做的.我永远不会对他的生活有什么影响.
Whatever he does, he does., I have no influence on his life what so ever.
麦琪:迈克,你最好讲,现在讲.你需要说些什么?
Maggie: Mike, you better talk and talk now.What have you got to say?
迈克:我真的,真的,真的爱你们.
Mike: I really, really, really love you guys.
本:算了吧,迈克.这是坚固的房间.
Ben: Forget it mike.It's a tough room.
迈克:好,好,
Mike: Ok, ok, I'll tell you everything and I wont hold back.
我告诉你们一切,丝毫不隐瞒.你告诉他们什么了?
How much have you told them?Ok, alright.
好,好吧.
Now little Bennie came to me with a very tough problem.
之后小本找我来解决一个难题.这样我本可以躲避,
Now I could have ducked it, but no.
但是我没有.我问自己,爸爸在这种情况下会说什么呢.
I asked myself what my father would have said in this situation.
我仅仅希望把这事说的短些,有趣些.
Only I'd make it shorter and a little more interesting.
迈克:本,你怎么变形了?
Mike: Ben, what are you all bent out of shape for?
我说,瞧瞧,
I mean look, lets face it,
要面对这个事情,
you are never going to date a girl on the A list.
你不会和一流的女孩子约会.和乐队的女孩约会算你幸运.
You'd be lucky to date a girl in band.
本:迈克,如果你这么说,
Ben: Mike, if you are going to say stuff like that,
我也许也可以跟爸爸谈了.
I might as well go talk to dad.
迈克:你上钩了.
Mike: You're butts off the hook.
本:谢了,迈克.
Ben: Thanks for nothing Mike.
迈克:嗨,本.说说.谁告诉你那个女孩不值?
Mike: Hey Ben.Look.Who ever told you that this girl was unworthy?
本:沃特,哈瑞和斯丁克.
Ben: Veto, Harry and Stinky.
迈克:别理他们.
Mike: Ignore them.
本:你告诉沃别理我的朋友?
Ben: You're telling me to ignore my friends?
迈克:不,我告诉你要结交一些新朋友.
Mike: No, I'm telling you to get some new friends.I mean think Bennie.
想想,本.不知什么原因,
Somehow, some girl finds you vaguely attractive,
一个女孩子发现你蛮有魅力的,但是你却另她失望.
and you are about to turn her down!
本:好啦.
Ben: Well,
迈克:听着,我这么说吧.
Mike: Look, let me put it this way.Did Mr.
海莉说过"我要等下一颗彗星"?
Hailey say I'll wait for the next comet?
麦琪:本,事情事这样的吗?
Maggie: Ben, it actually happened that way?
本:是.
Ben: Yeah.
杰森:我不知道说什么.
Jason: I don't know what to say.
你真的告诉他不要被外界的压力屈服.反对朋友的意见,
You really told him not to buckle to peer pressure?
做正确的事情?
To stand up to his friends and do the right thing?
迈克:是的.还有,如果她真的不顾一切,那么小本不是幸运了.
Mike: Yeah.And besides, if she's really desperate, the weenie might get lucky.
杰森:滚出去,迈克.
Jason: Get out Mike.
本:好了,我已经吸取教训了.我再也不跟迈克说话了.
Ben: Well I've certainly learned my lesson.I'll never talk to mike again.
麦琪:本,那个约会的事情呢?
Maggie: Ben, the date.
本:哦,是呀.
Ben: Oh yeah.
麦琪:本!
Maggie: Ben!
本:我在等待时机.
Ben: I'm waiting for the ripple.
电影院:我想我们迷路了,明迪.
Cinema: I think we're lost Mindy.This maze is so confusing.
这个迷宫真迷惑人.我们走不出去了.
We're never going to get out of here.
朗达:本,你真喜欢那个糊涂熊吗?
Ronda: Ben, you really like the fuzzy wuzzy bears?
本:是,他们很酷.
Ben: Yeah, they're cool.
朗达:那么去第四电影院看不是更有趣嘛?
Ronda: Wouldn't it be more fun to go over to cinema four and see Wild
At Heart?
本:不.我不喜欢过多的性和暴力.太暴力.
Ben: No.Excessive sex and violence upsets me.Violence anyway.
电影院:我爱你,小熊.
Cinema: I love you Windy bear.
沃特:他们在那.跟我说的一样.
Veto: There they are.Just like I said.
哈瑞:我真不敢相信.
Harry: I can't believe it.
小孩:嘘1安静.
Children: Shhh!Quiet.
本:哦!
Ben: Oh!
朗达:怎么回事?
Ronda: What's wrong?
本:对不起.我要去洗手间.
Ben: Excuse me.I have to go to the bathroom.Pick up some raisonettes.
顺便带点吃的.你们怎么也来看G级电影?
What are you guys doing at a G rated movie?
哈瑞:你和朗达 格林在干什么?
Harry: What are you doing with Ronda Green?
本:她也在这里.
Ben: She's here too.
沃特:很不错的尝试,
Veto: Nice try Bennie.
本.
So you guys think that he should wear that hall monitor sash over his
你们是不是觉得他应该把过道管理员的牌子戴在左肩或者右肩?
left shoulder or his right?
本:(沉思)我走上绝路了.我死了.
Ben: (in his mind) I was cornered.I was dead.My honor was at stake.
我已经没面子了.因此,我只有说谎.
So I lied.
本:你们都看错朗达了.她是个能让男孩子幸福的女孩.
Ben: You guys have got it all wrong about Ronda.
如果你们知道我的意思.
She's the kinda girl who makes guys happy.If you know what I mean.
我说多了,但是荧幕上有小糊涂熊.
I'd say more but there are little fuzzy bears on the screen.
哈瑞:但是她看起来很正经.
Harry: but she looks so moral.
本:听好,我不管你们怎么想,我很幸福.
Ben: Look, I don't care what you guys think, cos I'm happy.
哈哈,哈哈,哈哈!
Ha ha ha ha ha h a!
本:之后的几个小时是含糊不清.我所能确定的是,那晚朗达为我买第二个热狗的时候,我们的关系已经稳定了.我没想到谎言可以传播这么迅速.这大大改变了我的生活.人们盯着我看.但是他们没有嘲笑.
Ben: (in his mind) The next couple of hours were a blur.All I am sure of is by the time Ronda bought me that second chilidog later that night, we were going steady.I had no idea that one lie could spread so fast.It changed my life so much.People were looking at me.And they weren't laughing.
孩子们:欢迎.本,本!
Kids: Applause.Bennie, Bennie!
本:这是在杜威高中历史上的第一次,高一新生的名字被放进了真理墙.
Ben: (in his mind) For the first time in the history of Dewey High,
我的名字.
a freshman's name had been added to the wall of truth.My name.
我真的很感动.在第一周的周末,
I was sincerely touched.
她把东西搬进了我的橱柜.
By the end of the first week, she'd moved into my locker.
有点不方便,但是没关系,
It was a little inconvenient, but I didn't mind,
因为学校里的每个人都尊敬我.
cos everyone at the school was now treating me with respect.
包括门卫鲍勃.他甚至让我碰他的钥匙.
Including janitor bob.He even let me touch his keys.
杰森:因此你就和那个其实你不喜欢的女孩出去约会,就为了欺骗你的朋友?
Jason: So you are going out with a girl that you don't even like just to keep your friends fooled?
本:是.你明白了.
Ben: Yeah.Now you see.
杰森:好,你想娶那个女孩吗,
Jason: Alright, do you plan on marrying the girl,
还是仅仅继续演戏,本?
just to keep up the charade Ben?
本:不,我三年内毕业.然后通常去参军.
Ben: No, see in three years I graduate.Then there's always the army.
杰森:你不知道这样很出格吗?
Jason: You see this is really out there.
本:嗨,不全这样,爸爸.格林太太是个好厨师.
Ben: Hey, it's not all bad.Mrs.Green is a great cook.
麦琪:你在那里吃晚饭?
Maggie: You eat dinner there too?
本:是呀,不过是在这里吃完之后.
Ben: Yeah, but only after I eat dinner here first.
杰森:本!
Jason: Ben!
本:嗨,这是他们感谢我做那么多家务的方式.
Ben: Hey, it's their way of thanking me for doing all those chores.
麦琪:但是还有一件事情,本.
Maggie: But that's another thing Ben.
你上次在家做家务是什么时候?
When was the last time you did a chore around here?
本:因为我一直太累了.
Ben: Its just I'm always so tired.
杰森:我猜也是.
Jason: I guess so.
本:还有修理了转播器,我很幸运.
Ben: And about fixing his transmission, I got lucky.
麦琪:你的好运到头了,本.
Maggie: Well your luck just ran out Ben.
杰森:不能继续了.
Jason: This cannot go on.
本:我所做的真的错了吗?
Ben: What did I do that was really wrong?
麦琪:和一个我们从来没有见过的女孩约会.
Maggie: Dating a girl we never met.
杰森:和一个我们从来没有见过的女孩稳定关系.
Jason: Going steady with a girl we haven't met.
麦琪:第一,你不允许确定关系.
Maggie: When you aren't allowed to go steady in the first place.
杰森:你已经四十二次不经允许偷偷溜出家门.
Jason: Sneaking out of this house forty two times without permission.
麦琪:每晚吃两餐.
Maggie: Eating two dinners every night.
本:怎么错了?
Ben: How's that wrong?
麦琪:不对,就是不对.
Maggie: It's wrong.It's just wrong.
杰森:你对那个姑娘散布的所有谣言该怎么解决?
Jason: And what about all the rumors you are starting about this girl?
本:你不用担心谣言,爸爸.我解决.
Ben: You don't have to worry about the rumours dad.I made them up.
杰森:本,你就没有想过,你这样可能会损害那个女孩的名誉?
Jason: Ben has it occurred to you that you might be damaging this girls reputation
本:我不明白这.她现在是一流的.
Ben: I don't see how.She's on the A list now.
杰森:你认为你现在该做什么?
Jason: So what do you think you should do now?
本:我不知道.反正不会是吃晚饭.                                                                                                                                         朗达的父亲:朗达.我们养狗了?
Ben: I don't know.I know its not having dinner.(And so the next morning
Ronda's father: Here Robbie.Eh do we have a dog
朗达:没有呀.
Ronda: No.
朗达的父亲:如果有的话,就叫它罗比.
Ronda's father: If we did I'd call it Robbie.Ben, you knuckle head!
本,你这滑头!你来多久了?
How long have you been here?
本:黎明.
Ben: Since dawn.
朗达:你怎么一言不发?
Ronda: Then why didn't you say something?
我们可以早点挖池子.
We could have got an early start on digging the pool.
本;格林先生,朗达在家吗?
Ben: Mr.Green, is Ronda home?
朗达:在呀,但是她不会用铁铲.
Ronda: Yeah, but she's not much good with a shovel.
可能镐用起来很熟练.好象我需要告诉你似的.
Mighty handy with a pick axe though.Like I need to tell you.
哈哈,哈哈.
Ha ha ha ha.
本:我可以跟她谈谈吗?
Ben: Can I talk to her?
朗达:可以呀.进来,吃早餐.
Ronda: f Sure.Come in and have some breakfast.
本:哦,不了,我已经吃过了.
Ben: Um no, I cant I already ate.
朗达:真的?
Ronda: So.
本:错了.我不能告诉你为什么,就是错了.我可以跟朗达谈谈吗?
Ben: It's wrong.I can't tell you why, it's just wrong.Can I speak to Ronda?
朗达:我明白你的话.你这个小混蛋.朗达,你男朋友来了.嗨,我们有只小狗了.过来,罗比.过来,伙计.哦,哦,哦.小狗宝贝,小狗宝贝.我喜欢这个小笨蛋.嗨,朗达,瞧,谁来了.
Ronda: I got you.You devil.Ronda, your boyfriend's here.Hey, we do have a
dog.Come here Robbie.Come on fellow.Ho ho ho.Doggie noogies, doggie noogies.I
love this little knucklehead.Hey Ronda, look who's here
本:我怎么向她解释这一切?好了,
Ben: (in his head) How am I going to explain this to her?
我别无选择.
Ok, I've got no choice.I've got to be honest.
我得诚实.我告诉她,
I'll tell her I'm not attracted to her, I never was attracted to her,
我没有被她迷住,
and the only reason I'm dating her is because my friends believe my lies
从来没有,我与她约会的唯一原因是我的朋友相信我关于她的谎言.
about her.
朗达:哦,这么早,
Ronda: (in her head) Oh, what's he doing here this early?
她来这干什么?
This is the last straw.
这是最后的机会.
Today is the day I tell him that the only reason I went out with him
今天我告诉他,我跟他出去约会的唯一原因是想进入一流.
was to get on the A list.
朗达:本.
Ronda: Ben.
本:朗达.
Ben: Ronda.
本和朗达:勿失良机.
Ben and Ronda (in their heads): It's now or never.
本:我知道我早就来了,我不吃早饭.
Ben: Look I know I'm here early, I don't want breakfast.
我们分手吧?
Do you want to break up?
朗达:我也不饿.很好,我们分手.
Ronda: I'm not hungry either.Great, let's break up.
本:什么时候?
Ben: When?
朗达:现在就是好时候.
Ronda: Now's good.
本:好,学校见.
Ben: Ok, see you in school.
朗达:学校见.
Ronda: See you in school.
本:这是六个星期里的第一次她 高兴.
朗达:我也是.
00:21:16,000
Ben: (in his head) For the first time in six weeks, she's made me happy. Ronda: (in her head) Me too.